PG 160, Floods and Hurricanes in Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Series 4. Tropical Storm Irene, 2011
  - Department of Energy and Environmental Protection (DEEP) Photographs, 2011; 2 compact discs; 2012-018
    The approximately 59 digital photographs on compact disc 1 document Tropical Storm Irene damage in the towns of Guilford, Westbrook, Old Saybrook, Milford, Bristol, and East Haven. The approximately 385 digital photographs on compact disc 2 are from the Department of Energy and Environmental Protection (DEEP), Office of Long Island Sound Programs (OLISP) which document Tropical Storm Irene damage along the coast.
    This item is separated from the collection. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.